A good friend to meet, MBC
What are you doing there?
The scenery here is amazing
If you come and drink coffee
I think it would be perfect
Dahye is with me in this yard
Why do I want to drink coffee?
Mr. Dahye
I don't have any questions
Ah, I wonder
Why on earth did Dahee
You know, Manager Kwak from the PR team?
His friend used to be
I worked at the same company as Dahee.
Even then, people
People like this on the bulletin board
snipe
They said it got caught and turned over.
I don't even know that
Our Dahee
There is no one with a heavy mouth like Mr.
I revealed all my secrets
Oh boy, only Seungjae did that.
Uh uh sister hehe
Why is the ID called Hoppang?
White bread, garlic bread, pizza bread, why should I bake it?
I was curious about that
What about buns?
Enjoy the taste with just one bite
You can't know everything
hot is
Because it's hidden deeper inside
Me too
outwardly
If you smile and act kind,
People say that
You know it's my everything
Like a fool
Everyone who believed again now is a fool
It's handled
ha
It's really babyish
baby
So, this is what happened
With a real baby
Let's lie one more time
What
no
I had no choice but to do that too
There might be a story.
For example
I don't know people's hearts
A psychopath or something
Shut up
Not
Aliens that will wreak havoc on the world
That's not it either, it hasn't happened yet
Have a history of being abandoned by your parents?
What
I'm sorry, I'm being abandoned.
What will I be when I grow up?
Also, my nature is not gentle.
A child who doesn't even smile
Who would have liked it?
How many times have you been adopted and given away?
Going back to the orphanage
Difficult push while repeating
There was something that woke me up.
Ah
maybe
as it is
Maybe I can't do it
Will things be different when I become an adult?
I had expectations
Could it be that
place
It was the same
Work isn't just about work
You also need to know how to get along with people.
soon
A person with a pretty face
What's wrong
The doubts I've had since I was young
With confidence while working at the company
I've changed
Oh really
Yes, I shouldn’t live as myself.
From then on
people in the world like
I lived playing Jeong Da-hee.
Pretending to be nice
Pretending to be gentle
pretend to smile
Then at some point
I felt a little unfair.
He said he was having a fling with her.
He went around
yes
It's not like that.
Oh, by the way
And Jimin in the management support room.
You know, I don't drink anything.
I even wear a mask like this
I live while hiding myself
Sleeping without any worries
When I look at people who live openly
You're disgusting and angry.
So
Resolving my anger in my own way
I held on
Anyway, let's see
Although nothing was resolved
Besides, there's no such thing as a secret
Because it doesn't last long
If your identity is discovered
Moving companies again and again
How many times
boring
I lived that act over and over again.
Then one day
We met like a miracle
a person who resembles me
That person is sitting on a transparent chair
sitting down
I'm wearing a transparent mask
Trying to somehow blend in with the crowd
That look of effort
It looked so much like me
From then on, that person kept appearing in my eyes.
Da-hye gets stepped on.
That person doesn't give Dongwoo a chance.
Please eat this
Ah, I know you hate it
Only Americano on purpose
Even though I bought it for you
Wait a minute
on purpose
I know I don't like that
I said I did it on purpose
Why
so that
Under the pretext of apologizing, let’s eat together
Because I can buy it
Ha, you're really screwed up.
That's right
I should have just lived like a piece of shit.
What
If you draw shit, draw shit like that
back and forth
I have to roll over and get stuck in a corner.
Why did it fly away so suddenly?
Dahye said so
I keep
You want to get upset
Anyway, you are a human like me
Isn't it true?
Don't lose your strength and work together
Let's break it down
over and over again
You want to shake Dahye up.
What should we do together?
What's on the bulletin board
I should have written that anyway
What
It would have been nice if that were the case haha
Dahye said that
People will just cover it up
I really care about Dahye.
People who love me
So broken
Are you just going to cover up for Dahye?
Okay
Because I understand
I hate it once I come down.
If you go down now
With a smile
Please believe it was a misunderstanding
I have to lie again
I don't want to do that anymore.
There's no reason to do it
So that's it
What are you doing? What are you doing?
uh
Oh, what are you doing? Let go of this.
Why you shouldn't die
Ha let me know
Oh, on a Friday like today
There is death
Lady, let go of this, really.
I have to go ice speeding on the weekend.
What?
Cleaning room on a golden weekend at work
are you crazy
I'm good
Black clothes you don't even wear
expensive because of you
I'll have to leave the blow dryer to you.
Oh, it hurts.
So
Don't die, live
Try to survive and hold on
I know again
change
It might be possible
It will be different
You can be brave, right?
A moment like that for you too
You can come
Oh, Ji-hye, I checked your condition.
Yes, I finished checking it as soon as I got to work.
But I heard a defect was found. Yes.
Oh uh uh wait a second
If a defect is found there
Contact the logistics center directly
Phone number is here
Oh yes sorry
What did Jihye do before joining the company?
Oh, I
While working part-time
I'm ready to join the company
Wow, that must have been hard
Do you want to prepare for a part-time job?
Still we
Cheer up and try hard
Dear Insu
Because the period is not long
I'm a little impatient too.
Yes I will do my best
Haha
If you look at it this way
yes
really
Really
What, why do I think of that at this time?
Yeah
Mr. Jaeseong, the copy you talked about back then.
Take your annual leave
where to go
Ah, China.
Haha, I have something to do because you gave me a letter.
What kind of annual leave is it?
I'm so busy, yes
Oh, that's okay, that's okay, but
Do you ever meet that foreign boyfriend again?
why
What are you two going to do when you go to China?
Oh, that's not it
I have my own personal reasons.
Because we are busy right now
Apply next time
Yes, I understand.
That's why Jisong couldn't pay annual leave.
Jisong is at that house.
Go to China and Tanghulu
Make it yourself
I guess I was trying to learn
But I can't go
today
I will try to practice on my own somehow.
No, but why do I practice at work?
And I fell asleep
mom
pot while doing it at home
Burn it and eat it
I told my sister I almost died.
No but
I scraped all the chicken off the bottom of the pot.
Ahahaha
He's best friends with the manager.
He told me to just clean up and leave.
There's a long way to go, a long way to go
But where are we going now?
we won't go far
I'm going to go to karaoke
Karaoke yeah
Mistress
Haha
Even if we meet
Be on my side
older sister
Oh why
Dr. Hey Han
Two hours of singing alone
You could have called me
Twelve times in a hundred-point panpare
It's okay if it makes you cry
Is it not enough?
It's not enough haha
It's not enough
Dr. Han is not enough
sister
I'm so tired
I miss Dr. Han so much
How can I endure something like this?
What should I do?
I
how to overcome
let me know
Yeah
I have to admit it
That I can't get over it
ha
What
What a painful and difficult time
you
Like skipping tube ads
I thought I could skip it.
Just goth with your whole body
Those painful times
You have to go through this gruesomely.
Then, at some point,
It gets better
It'll be okay
Oh, what do you mean it’s going to be okay?
Oh, I don't know
Well, then the people of the world
They say it gets better
I'm not sure
In the first place I
I thought it would be okay
Because I have never
I've never even tried that
still just
On the most painful day in the world
I'm living with one foot in the water
Hey, you're sad
Haha hey
Ugh
yes cry
Crying also comes from the inside.
Tell me when you're all crying
me tomorrow
Briefing on our plans
I said I would do it
plan for tomorrow
why
what are we doing
Wow, what kind of shit car is this?
Hey, I keep pooping somewhere.
I paid quite a bit for it.
Our other people’s hearts too
Much more than I rode
I think it sucks
A
Hey, this navigation works well too.
Look at this, the sunroof also opens.
Hehe
Oh my sister
Oh, this is crazy. Why is this closed?
Be in a good mood, kid
We change our mood with something like this
Oh how good it is
I saw it
Coins went up more, yes
I heard there was a network update
The rise was unstoppable.
At this point
I'm going to sign a contract for the store right away.
Ah, that store
I'm trying to find out properly.
I looked into it.
and
I want to leave the company quickly
I'm dying to see that Team Leader Song too.
Oh Dae-ri, yes too.
Oh Dae-ri, why are you
kid just just
Because it’s boring in many ways, um
You know that
Just hold on to that spirit and just work
I want to do it
Yes, I believe in our Jisong
Our Jisong is fine now too
Because I'm an adult
Of course
Even today, it's all right outside
Because I pay it.
uh
Yeah, where are we going?
Oh, I'm in the countryside
They said they would show me the statement from the dinner table.
uh
Eating gondre while looking at the countryside
rice set meal
How delicious
What is my sadness?
Will it be solved with gondre?
Haha
Oh my, what is it, sister, sister, sister?
It's raining. It's raining. Close it. Close it.
What is it?
Close it uh uh
Oh, hey, hey, hey, why is this not working?
Why can't I do this?
That that
Hey, this doesn't work
Ah
Why is this water seaweed?
Hey, hey, take off our heads.
Take my head off
Ah ah ah what is it
What is this
I can't see it
Oh, where are we going?
Sister, sister, I knew.
uh
How about the car, sister?
Ah
I can't deliver long distances in this car.
Oh, what do you mean, delivery?
Oh actually
I bought this car to make money.
No errand center green house
delivery taxi
How many things can you do with a car?
Just because you quit the company
You can't just play around.
Well then
My sister made money
in the end
You chose to make money again.
Wow, it's a mess, it's a mess
Wow
uh sister uh
What should I do when the fire truck comes in?
How do I pull it back?
Oh my, why doesn’t this work? Oh my.
Oh, why doesn’t this work again?
No way
What should I do? I’m on the move upset.
Please remove the car, yes.
Oh yes, I want to do that too.
Now wait a minute
This doesn't reach me well
Come on, come on, hurry up!
Oh my sister
Hey hey hey let's go out and push
Uh oh, push it quickly, push it
Oh wait a minute
sorry
one two three
Are you pushing?
Ah
Why are you pushing?
Ah, I don’t think it will work out for you.
Oh, oh, what's wrong?
Wow
why
Hurry up. Has it fallen outside?
Oh wait, one two three the end
Now
Ah, the status difference is moving.
Eight children identified in overturned bus
Oh sister
I guess the babies had an accident.
mom
Daycare center running in the rain
School bus in Seoul city
in one borough
collided with the guardrail
Four people were injured in this accident
five years old
One girl died
The child who died immediately after the accident
He was taken to the hospital in cardiac arrest
In the end, death occurred
Let's go
Just hit it and go.
uh uh
uh
What should I do, sister?
this afternoon
Around one o’clock, Gochon, Gimpo-si, Gyeonggi-do
On the way to an event in the app
daycare center
The bus to go to school
A rollover accident occurred
Report immediately after the accident
The fire department received
quickly on site
A rescue operation was launched.
Fortunately
All passengers were rescued safely.
He was transported to a nearby hospital.
The vehicle in which the accident occurred was a daycare center.
eight students
I don't think anyone was seriously hurt.
Oh thank goodness
Oh my, I almost fell, really.
Oh this
When pulling up
The lower part is all damaged.
Well, I am completely ignorant.
There is no need to salvage any parts just for this one.
Keep doing this
On the highway while trying to get on
Rather than just stop on the highway
Better stop now
Please scrap the car
yes yes
I'm serious.
no sister
Still this car
I didn't buy it for a lot of money.
It'll be okay
It's okay then
no
It's more than okay
Guys
I'm going to stop riding the Exy now.
I like that car too
stop now
I think it's time
I made money
be happy in life
It's not just work
I still feel sad and angry
There are things to do, but the important thing is
where are we
What to focus on
Isn't it a matter of making a choice?
I'd rather keep going
I choose to stop here
I want to rest now
I think it will work now
What do you guys do?
Jiyong Kim
Don't use my annual leave
I did, but it was cute and written well.
yes
Annual leave is based on writing.
Legally guaranteed to the writer
It's a right
Then it's right
Mr. Kim Yoo-seong
What do you know, kid, what do you know about the law?
Oh, I know how.
If you keep doing this
I don't know, but I'm hiring
The lawyer knows, right?
Until now I
Are you afraid of poop so you avoid it?
I don't avoid it because it's dirty.
When I think about it, whether it's scary or dirty
I don't think it's something to avoid.
When you see a poop
I have to clean it up like
poop again
poop
Ah ah
What you're saying is that I'm shit right now
uh
Jooyoung Kim
I'm crazy, why?
fair annual leave
You're being ridiculously abusive with what you write.
language without sin
Violent and often like this
Get your hands dirty too
The team leader who makes fun of you is the one
I'm not crazy.
Ah
If I quit now
I won't even call you team leader.
uncle
Ah
Aja
Mr. Aja
Wow, you're really crazy. Really.
Really, really, baby
If you do this, dad
Ah
Really, what are you guys?
It's crazy
Sure
I just asked him if he was coming, so he was really Mr.
What are you doing, Mr. Oh?
Why are you suddenly doing this to me?
No, Mr. Ji-seok
Are you quitting the company?
That thing you threw earlier was a resignation letter.
Even though I don't even know what it is right now, I'm on my side
Did you eat it?
Oh, it's me
It's okay if you quit, but Mr. Oh.
What are you going to do?
Hey, what is it?
Oh, and I'll take your side because it's worth it.
Jisung, why can’t he use his annual leave?
and in fact last
Jisung from the end of the month
I stayed up all night alone
I made a mistake with the settlement this time.
Jisung too
You betrayed me all by yourself.
Jisung is leaving the company
I really hate it but
Still, Mr. Jisung
Everything Jisung wants
I am a person who is qualified to do this.
Cover my eyes
yes
ah yes
Ah now
I trust my intuition
I'm trying to start a business.
I keep feeling like this
What if I eat it wrong?
What was wrong?
I didn't think you'd be excited
Never, Oh Dae-ri.
I thought you wouldn't be excited.
But if you keep making my heart flutter like this
If you lose it
What should I do?
I quit so suddenly
I'm so sorry
We just get goosebumps
There was a bit of an unpleasant incident.
I can't misunderstand
It's a bit disappointing to unpack it.
Still
Being able to work with you
It was really good
Well then, let’s get into it.
Oh, it's a bit embarrassing.
I was at that time
I'm pretty
touching
I thought I made a comment
How is it that nothing has changed?
Um well
What did you expect?
Take this
Snack subscription box
not yet secure
You know there are so many dots.
I think you need to work a little harder.
Oh Mr.
ever
It's an acquisition
What was done
I organized it into a file.
In this
Because there is everything from one to ten.
What's confusing?
If you have it, look for it here.
yes thank you
Ah
If you time it right, you can do it alone for ten minutes
Oh no
You can rest for about twenty minutes
That's where it is
If you work hard and have a hard time
Go somewhere like this and get some rest.
I can't rest when I'm having a hard time
Because I can't cry when I need to be sad
that something
I felt a little broken
Jihye, don’t do that. Yes, whenever you have time.
Go slowly, cry and rest
That way it lasts long
yes
Mr. Eunseong
Ah
Baby, something big is wrong now.
You're crying
Sleep well, work hard
to evil
Don't live only with evil and gangsterism
If you crave kkangsoju
Be sure to contact me anytime
really
Contact us
for a moment
Yes haha
Yes, this promotion personnel team
Team Leader Choi prayed, no, Lee Lee.
This time, I am definitely Team Leader Choi.
I live with my mother-in-law
Just be my own child
and what
Hee-sa Kim is also an alumnus, yes.
Our national team hyung is
Let's all aim together, yeah
Ah
I'm going crazy
What are you saying?
At least use a coin
Ah
Oh, I'm really excited
It's so cold and absurd
Really no where
crazy bitch boss
I resigned from the cafeteria.
Oh and when do I touch it
I touched it and when
What a year
Same team leader
If you live well,
You should be thankful
Where are you cheeky on the subject?
How much money do you have with that coin?
The very arrogance I earned pierced the sky
Just anyway
These days, things don't boil down to a concept.
Eat it up, Mr.
Why are you sitting like that right now?
ha
Eunsang goes out
Now the road ahead of me is dark
It's scary
ha
But I didn't really touch it.
I passed by, I passed by
The thing that passed by is just a slap
Oh my brother
This bastard is such a vicious bastard.
I'm talking uh
I'm really into things these days
It's an ego trial
taken from the company
I just didn't want to see you doing this.
Hey you bastard
Even if it were me, I would do the same.
What a shitty company.
more shitty boss
I feel this way too, but they
How amazing is this?
Why can't they think of other things?
Hey Lee, what are you doing?
Why am I because of a bastard like you?
Do you need to understand your heart?
Ten thousand times
Mr. Lee, are you saying you can’t live like an old man?
Mr. Hwak
Hey hey hey it's ancient ancient spirit
Hey, let’s go, where did you give it to?
Hey that one
Why are you like that?
He said he doesn't want to work at a raw fish company.
Oh, I see.
Ah, why am I like that?
I like going to work
As long as there are no old guys like you
Hey
The day I quit my job
Do I have to stay here until night?
Haha, I'm really bored.
um
What do I do when work ends late?
Now
Everyone say a word before the big day
Oh well that's it
Can it be summed up in one word?
We also have the power to turn this game around.
A secret medicine
I don't think I can see
You guys are so bad at falling down
You guys let’s go let’s go
Let's go, let's go
Get ready and let's go
I
I will go with you until the end
us
Then let's go all the way to the end.
let's keep going
Still
If I had to leave a word
I
I'm free
Kang Eun-sang also worked hard.
Jisung Kim worked hard too.
Haha
And in this part
Ta-da
Has there been a collaboration?
Oh, congratulations on your escape!
More than congratulating a child
I need to say thank you
We told you
Yeah
I even dare to imagine
This kind of life I can't even see if I'm greedy
For letting me live
And like this
Drag me into a wonderful story
For giving me
Thank you, sister
Hmm
Me too
Thank you so much, sister
I love you
Haha right
Oh hey hey it tickles like crazy hey
Fall away haha
uh
Wow
What are you recommending?
There is a university nearby.
uh
It's perfect
perfectly beautiful
Everyone
It's a beautiful night
let's go
Won't you be lonely?
Ah
I quit my job
ha
I can sleep more
Ah
um
that filled my sister's life
Where numbers and goals disappear
The moment of mourning has arrived
My sister is finally here
crying properly
Like a person who realized the way
I cried endlessly
I cried as much as I wanted
sister
The chairman has gone
uh
Or
How long have you been crying in earnest?
I don't know where I went, I don't know
But
Let's just see one more time
Come and cry endlessly
What happened to your store deposit?
I can't get it back
Just what
I have to pay tuition for life.
Jisong was scammed
Jisong goes
The place where the medicine was placed is fake
It was a mess
It must have been shocking enough.
Jisong is no longer
Long time for one failure
Didn't stay or get frustrated
you are really fine
I need to shake it off quickly.
I got something new too, hmmm
Hey
Our Jisong has really grown up now.
Let's go right now
What should I do?
and
I
Ha, it's always nice to see you
Well, it would have been better if we were together
With me
Will you marry me?
Ah
I miss you
July 20th, 1969
Apollo Eleven is Human
first on the moon
It was a historic moment when
But what we need to pay attention to is
Changryuk
It might be a later story
Actually, going to the moon isn't the end.
Which way should I take next?
Now I
which direction
What's more important is whether you're watching
But that's
It's hard to know on your own.
Apollo Twelve with Earth
Because we communicated endlessly
We were able to land safely on the moon.
Humanity vividly remembers that moment
Because I was able to watch
In that sense, communication is
It's about finding out each other's direction.
we can walk together
Adjust your path little by little
Isn’t it a process?
Then at work
More about the importance of communication
Let me give you an example
The owner's mango tanghulu came out.
yes thank you
No, the boss
The store will do well like this
How did you know
Do you have a good sense?
Well, there were times when it felt good.
But at that time
All I can do is believe that my intuition is good.
I'll trust you with my life
Because there is nothing
I think I was just obsessed with it.
Well then
that's my life
Should I say it felt like the biggest weapon?
Not now. Why not now?
Now I'm my life
It's the biggest weapon haha.
Just wait and see
Tanghulu within a few years
It will become more popular
Because
I will definitely make it like that
I hope so
No, the building owner here
They pay the monthly rent really cheaply.
Boss, it would be perfect to become rich.
Oh my, really
Thank you
Oh mom this
Because the seasons have changed
I need to wear new clothes too.
Mom, I liked this color
Oh, something like this
Thank you, I’ll take a look
Oh right
And this
Jisong’s favorite thing about her mom
I wrapped it for you
This is strawberry and grape Tanghulu
no
You can do business like this.
Please tell me that I will eat well.
Oh, that's right, and this is my dad's.
me what
Ah
I accept any color well.
Besides grapes and strawberries
I also eat tomatoes very well haha.
Pay my cell phone bill
Yeah
That's it, you have to pay it
Ugh annoying
Wait a minute
don't be like that
Oh, I hate it
I live by gaining weight.
How much would it be like to be shriveled up like that?
Don't you think it's annoying?
what am i
But your dad couldn't do it all
It's not like that
Well then, what did I do well?
your dad though
I didn't do drugs.
I didn't even commit murder.
Oh my gosh, stop it.
What these days
It seemed like I was studying stocks, but
It's useless again and again
No, if I have to make a living, I
Go to work yeah
Did you just work to make a living?
Mom, whose side are you taking now?
Taking sides
I don't have a salty life.
Oh no
Yes hehehehe
Yeah
Hey, let's go already
Hey, I bought this ice cream.
do i know
Oh no
Wow, I still bought yours with this cone.
How can it be like this?
I don't kill, I don't do drugs
daughter
I buy ice cream in cones.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to do filial piety, but I can't not do it.
Oh what is this
The operation is
Yeah
No, there is something you want to do.
Because I see it
Dad is a four-leaf clover on the ground
I can't find one
I'm blessed by nature
I want to do this on that topic
I have a lot of desire to do that.
Who can criticize that
I was like that too
So just once
Trust me and go for it
You see, this one time I
I will be your father's luck
Dahyeya
Still too far
Don't have it
Go as far as you can
Oh please
Hey, it's different this time
I really studied a lot
Look for that report too.
Watch the performance announcement as well.
I even watched the CEO interview.
What is your name?
You know that
the mask
Is that Elon mask?
that
That sock is the captain
you forward
This electric car
The era of popularization will surely come
are you real this time
Oh my, I'm giving up
Hey
Even if you smile like that, it's real
This is what dad always does
I said it was really really real
No, it was my Jin at that time
I thought it was true
This is because I studied a lot
This is
Dad said he studied back then too.
Hey, if it rains, the ground gets wet.
Oh, that's the same thing
Oh what
I can’t do it, give it to me, really, kid.
Yes, Lee Joo-ah from Gwanak-gu
This is the song you requested.
I enjoyed Ham Ji-woo’s song.
Some people may know something
This person
I am a singer active in the English-speaking world.
fortress
It's quite popular in Korea too.
This person was interviewed before.
Ah, it's fun
Ah, I
comforting to someone
I don't want to do music
Enough to need comfort
people's lives
It's too hard
I don't want you to be lonely
In people's very, very good moments
just
I want to make music that celebrates
Oh, my song is so calming
Copyright
There won't be a lot of yoga coming.
Don't worry baby
When working at work
Because I received a lot of bonus
It's okay
So everyone, be happy.
surely
be happy
Ah, it's fun
I heard you'll be performing in Korea soon.
I should go there too
It looks like my ex-boyfriend is performing.
ex-boyfriend
Tuna, tuna
How does my selfishness jump out?
So
We must have that in our waiting room.
You need to set it up
That's recruiting our team
It's a prerequisite
Yes, but this time, I’m sorry.
Now We Are Already in Korea
At next time
If you invite me again, hey
At that time, Berry, thank you, thank you.
So what
The detailed schedule is
go then
communication again
Just do what you do
Ah, the event fee
Okay bye
Hey you
how to pay for the event
Only when talking like that is a native
Is it okay? It’s noisy.
This small theater with double speed
I'm in Manchester to perform.
Giving up on performing for a living
Do you think this makes sense?
Why is the size of the venue important?
The meaning is important
No, that means
Let me explain again.
contacted for a year
If you haven't done it,
It's a break up
we did that
Let's call it a breakup
I said we agreed
Why are you like this?
I just
in a good way
I came to Korea to perform
We also make Korean fans
Proceeds are also donated.
how good is this
I think you should take the donation.
How did you cheat all this time?
Are you just wearing trash?
My feet hurt
I can’t wear shoes because my feet hurt.
I
Yes, it must hurt
It's still going to hurt, yeah
Just eat it
I can do it, but I'm not a child.
Because this is heavy
It's going to be a little difficult for Ji Sungjae.
I can do it
You must be busy with your child's work.
Help me like this every time
kid what
You can exercise haha, just for fun.
I'm done with English
intelligence
Why are you like this?
How did you get here?
I saw Jisung and looked around the store.
Doing both the job and the job
When did you learn to say that again?
No, Jisung is my Korean
I told you I'm not good at it
So I learned
um
Well done
Well, he’s as handsome as you
A foreigner who is fluent in Korean
That concept totally works. It’s cute.
If I have time, I'll go on a trip
I can guide you
I also want to visit Namsang sometime.
guide
Yes, I started from Namsan
Fully cooked pork belly
I'll go out to the course and guide you.
I also enjoy eating pork belly.
What did Assistant Manager Woo say?
ah ah no
That trash
I'm going to take out the trash.
No no that
Oh, you're with me below.
no no sorry
If you have any difficulties in the future, be sure to
contact me
We are close to that level.
Because we are friends
yes
Manager Oh
Oh, let's do it together.
child
You can do it alone, but why did you come out?
Not yet, no, it’s okay, yeah
Ah still
thank you
Why one person
I'm not waiting
Oh, I went
I went
Ah ah ah
It's been a while since I came here, there's more
Why did you go in such a hurry?
um
He also has his own private life.
I guess I have an appointment.
no
What other promises did you make to Ji Seong-sil?
No, what kind of privacy do you have?
yes
ha
Mr. Jisung, I am no longer the assistant manager.
I'm the team leader
Not long ago, Team Leader Song
You left the company and I was promoted.
Oh, I'm the team leader, really.
No, but why?
You're only saying this now.
And some time ago
I went to the store
There was a time when I couldn't come out for about three days.
uh
At that time, gallstone removal surgery was not possible.
I'm here
I have a large polyp.
No, why are you saying that now?
Oh, are you okay now? And again.
What else is there
Oh, sure
I also have my own personal life.
Because it’s not that important.
Oh, what I'm saying is really funny.
I know
No matter how much I think about it
As much as Mr. Ji-dong
Nothing important
There is no need for privacy or anything like that.
in my life
As much as Mr. Continuity
There is nothing I want to do
So
I
Ah
Why are you doing this?
too
It's like a double body.
No, why are we like this?
that cool
I can't get anything from a man
I know very well that I can't give it to you
Ah I
What else
Jisung, with such a trivial confession
I'll try to shake your heart
Confession
No, while we were dating above
What kind of confession do I need again?
Yes yes yes
no
I'm dating
we're dating
We're dating
That uh
Then we're not dating, okay?
a year ago
Why did I tell that story?
Never, Oh Dae-ri.
I thought you wouldn't be excited.
Oh that's it
Ah, Mr. Oh, yes yes
What have we done so far?
no
Mr. Oh, what have you been doing so far?
Ah
The name of the store while we were dating
why do you help me
Why do you always take me home?
That's right
No but still
Dating is
We're not dating.
Oh me
I haven't even held your hand once.
Oh that's it
Because Audrey is that kind of character.
I thought we were making progress slowly.
Then catch it now uh
that
no
I couldn't even hug you
Then hug me now
that
yet
There must be one more thing I couldn't do, yeah
uh kid
Oh my, I'm so embarrassed ugh
This is really it
I'm crying
no no
No, no, don't cry at this timing.
don't cry
If you cry, I'll go
I'm going now
No way
I went that far
Because it’s not head-to-head
I can't do it.
Ah Tana
I'm not working hard
Dahye Jeong
A person who has more than me
So
don't avoid me
I'm being punished
What about Dr. Han?
These days, I really, really
It's a dream I cherish.
With me
Will you marry me?
how was it
I liked the live version better than the music version.
Ah
Yes, I liked it haha
It's good, but why didn't you get married?
I was really curious what it looked like
I finally see it now
Could it be that
Jiwoo finally looks happy now
I think it's all thanks to the lady
thank you
Oh, that
Oh Jisung, unnie
I got a call from Eunsang.
Now, when you hit me, don’t hit me in Japanese.
What kind of fan am I?
What is this again?
Now you have become a real hero.
Congratulations
I will always support you
Guys
Strawberry jam from breakfast today
Because the lid doesn’t open
I almost opened my head
Then
Ah
When did my daughter become so strong?
I ate a lot and played a lot.
Where can I run around and play in the cold?
It must be especially cold with you around.
Yeah
What are you talking about, mom?
When will spring come?
It's spring all over the world, yeah
Mom is so
I cry so the ice melts
You threw it away
Ji Sang-ah
It's warm now, mom
So mom goes to play now too
Everyone run and go play
I knew then
Ah
I guess my sadness has opened up a little bit.
maybe one more time
I guess we can get started.
In that sense
I'm thinking of playing one more time
What would be a good name for the new playground?
Eunsang Town Ground Villa
It's not even that, it's an okay street
Actually, I haven't decided on a name yet.
From now on, let’s slowly make it together
Guys, come and play quickly
Huh
Did Jisong bring the monthly rent? Huh?
Dahyeya
Sister Sister
Eunsang is back
how was it
I had a lot of fun
It's okay now, yeah
It's okay
I don't want to lose
But
I have to take it out little by little throughout my life.
There is also sadness
how about you guys
What has changed since you earned money?
What
Money is calling for money.
Our store is right here in Geumgum.
Business is the best
Oh, I guess I should get a rent increase.
Haha I look like a tree
Eat, work, sleep
rest sometimes
I stand with people and take off my clothes.
But
set out to make money
I can look forward to tomorrow more
I feel like I have strength
uh
I look forward to tomorrow every day these days
um
Is tomorrow really the only thing to look forward to?
Is it only tomorrow?
really
Oh what did you say
Ah, the only thing I’m really looking forward to is tomorrow.
Yes, team leader
Yes, the workshop went well.
no no
I'll get off work right away
There are times when I hear it
Ah
Just
I need some reorganization in my mind.
you
You're such a brat
Dr. Han
After seeing each other for a year, I just
I'm going
Ah, that day
Because of that situation
But I just didn't come
I left a card
I didn't leave a lingering feeling.
I really saw that and we were done
I thought it was
what are we doing
open
I thought you were the main character in the ending
no what
I just
Dr. Han is me.
Like I said I was rooting for you
I do that too
Why are you crying again?
How much I missed you
lie
It's true
I want to make international calls every night
I've been patient for so long, but do you know that?
I don't know
Plane tickets too
Daily reservation button
I got to the point where I could press it and then barely
I said I endured it.
Do you know that?
I didn't know
How much I missed you
Later, I said I saw a lot of nonsense.
I
I studied so much that I went crazy
I thought it was
What is it
A person desperately wanted to see
I'm confessing
There's no reaction
Why don't you talk, it scares people
It's not that you talk too much
I've given up all my greed
The dream is
I lost everything
no
I didn't lose one
Dr. Han
I really, really cherish it
It's a dream
So
Please keep dreaming
Then
Why don't you join in now?
ha
I love you
Jihoon Han
A story like this
So
People who desire more
how is the story
Should it end?
Being punished for being greedy
Is such a bad ending natural?
Life always defies expectations
We even spent time in the prediction department
ready to enjoy
So that's enough
Happy ending for everyone
There's nothing that can't be done, oh
write
Oh, that's strange.
Why did I just smell it but I was unlucky?
Coffee is usually used
Just eat what you are given.
Koo Dae-young
Yes yes boss
What, you weren't the boss?
What should I give you?
Oh please again
It's more delicious and more popular anyway.
It's better
Why so I can go far